<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>Starling Farchecker - Anarchist</title>
    <link href="https://cripplethepolice.pages.dev/tags/anarchist/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/>
    <link href="https://cripplethepolice.pages.dev/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2024-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://cripplethepolice.pages.dev/tags/anarchist/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Cripple the Police</title>
        <published>2024-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-06-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <author>
          <name>Unknown</name>
        </author>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://cripplethepolice.pages.dev/main/" type="text/html"/>
        <id>https://cripplethepolice.pages.dev/main/</id>
        
        <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have the authority to kill a minority.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fuck that shit, &#x27;cause I ain&#x27;t the one&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for a punk motherfucker with a badge and a gun&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to be beating on and thrown in jail.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The song caught the attention of the FBI, which sent a letter to Priority Records about N.W.A’s album. Although the FBI did not refer to “Fuck Tha Police” by name, their letter claimed the album “encourages violence against and disrespect for the law enforcement officer.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;hr &#x2F;&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;fuck-the-police&quot;&gt;Fuck the Police&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Fuck Tha Police&amp;quot; by the N.W.A is an important cultural step to recognize the
violence of the system we live in. Their hit album made
criticisms of the police in popular culture acceptable and even popular. We all know that the
police in the USA is unjust and cruel. A continuation of this movement in more
recent times brought about by the  muder of George Floyd, &amp;quot;Defund the police&amp;quot; tried to instill institutional changes. But police brutality
still exists. Systemic violence still exists. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from individual cases of police brutality, the police have a stranglehold on cultural and social change in the USA. A
peaceful protest is helpless against a militarized police. You must protest on
&lt;em&gt;their&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; terms, abide by &lt;em&gt;their&lt;&#x2F;em&gt; laws, while working to change the system that
they help maintain.  And they can accomplish that task very well. They have considerably more tools, both lethal and
non-lethal, to repress any movement that threatens the ruling class. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;America values the police because they resist change. They are the guard dogs of
capital. What hope do we have of defunding the police, instituting change within
the very entity that the government wields to resist change. No matter how loud
we shout, how unruly society becomes, the police will always be there with the
means to restore
society to its former order. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the true reason why it seems that protests and demonstrations do not
work in America in fostering institutional change. Institutional change happens
when the ruling class maintain a healthy fear and respect towards the general
population. When a militarized police comes in between the general population
and the ruling class, the ruling class becomes complacent and isolated from the
general population, and instead of serving the interest of society they serve
the interests of the ruling class.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, the ruling class needs to learn to hear our voices. We can start by
crippling the police.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;know-your-enemy&quot;&gt;Know your Enemy&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something must be done&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About vengeance, a badge and a gun&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Know your Enemy, by Rage against the Machine&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must know our enemy. The enemy are the ones that resist cultural and societal
change, maintain the current order of society, and proliferate war and death. &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.ochaopt.org&#x2F;content&#x2F;hostilities-gaza-strip-and-israel-flash-update-168&quot;&gt;37,000
people&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
so far have been killed in the Palestinian genocide, a genocide that the ruling
class have the means of ending (for example, by &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;press.un.org&#x2F;en&#x2F;2024&#x2F;sc15670.doc.htm&quot;&gt;recognizing Palestine as a UN
member, which the US vetoed&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;).
Even with the mass protests of university students in the US, there are no signs
of change in the US policy. Media focuses on the mass destruction of campus
facilities while overlooking the fact that the student-led movement and their
voices are being ignored. Instead, the police swoops in and declares an end to
their protests after a couple of weeks, once they&#x27;ve had their fun.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is important to know your enemy, more so to define who &lt;strong&gt;aren&#x27;t&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; your enemy.
Here are a list of people who aren&#x27;t enemies:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Civilians. Americans, regardless of whether they lean left or right, or
even whether they &amp;quot;back the blue&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Small businesses.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Firefighters, paramedics, park rangers, and people whose jobs it is to actually save lives
and protect and serve.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In contrast, here are a list of enemies. They are enemies because they resist
change by definition:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The police, because they protect the ruling class.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ruling class. Not just elected officials, but those with tremendous and
disproportionate wealth in society. Those that own a significant portion of
the country.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that we have defined the enemy, now let us discuss how to cripple our
enemies. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;rules-of-engagement&quot;&gt;Rules of engagement&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burn, burn, yes, you&#x27;re gonna burn&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burn, burn, yes, you&#x27;re gonna burn&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burn, burn, yes, you&#x27;re gonna burn&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bombtrack, by Rage against the Machine&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have defined the pieces and the board we are playing in, so now we must define
the rules of the game.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;no-violence&quot;&gt;No Violence&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make no mistake. This is a non-violent movement, but it does not mean that this
is a peaceful movement. Laws will be broken, property will be destroyed, and
there will be chaos. But there will be no casualties. Crippling the police does
not mean an all-out war against the police. Police officers, at the end of the
day, when they take off their badge and uniform and clock out of work, are
American civilians that come home to their families. Let us not forget this
fact, no matter how brutal the police becomes. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;destroy-police-property-and-divert-their-attention&quot;&gt;Destroy police property and Divert their attention&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To effectively cripple the police, we must destroy the means that they have to
repress societal change and deploy their brutality. I&#x27;m writing here about a
plan and a set of tactics that we can employ to this end.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stab the wheels of police cars, destroy their windows, steal their equipment,
take their guns away. Vandalize police departments. Nullify and pacify the police. That is our goal. Make it
impossible to do their jobs. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No explosives&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. Explosives scare people, and we want to be on their side. It
is too easy to cause collateral casualties with explosives. Molotov cocktails
provide a less dangerous substitute. Use with care and precision.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#x27;s an additional list of things that would make it impossible to do their
jobs, or at least fear abusing their power:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make a list of exceptionally brutal officers. List their name, face, and
addresses in public. And for people involved with this movement that are in
close proximity to these officers, report their location in real time.
They can be called &amp;quot;shadows,&amp;quot; and following and reporting bad officers&#x27;
movements can be called &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;shadowing the police.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can start with this. Here is a link to the video of the &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;ag.ny.gov&#x2F;osi&#x2F;footage&#x2F;win-rozario&quot;&gt;murder of Win
Rozario&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. The murderers are:
&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.50-a.org&#x2F;officer&#x2F;G7VR&quot;&gt;Matthew Cianfrocco&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;www.50-a.org&#x2F;officer&#x2F;QJDK&quot;&gt;Salvatore
Alongi&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siphon their attention&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. Make fake 911 calls of very brutal acts being perpetrated,
provide a location, and then flee the scene (or, if you want to, hide and record the
scene). This act is deemed successful if
it draws one or more police cars and police officers to the scene for a long
time to investigate. Bonus points if the police cars are vandalized during
the scene.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We must take care not to overload the 911 infrastructure too heavily, as this
is also the primary way civilians access critical emergency services like
the fire department and paramedics. I would estimate that the 911 infrastructure can handle about a
couple calls a day of this nature.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;hr &#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over time, there will be more creative and intricate ideas that we can employ to
safely cripple the police. I am open to ideas to expand this list. Here is my
SimpleX chat to communicate with me directly: &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;img&#x2F;IMG_20240604_201638.png&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;anonymity&quot;&gt;Anonymity&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brave the shadows, find the truth&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zed&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the most important part. Communication, coordination, and trust is key.
We need each other for the movement to be successful. Those that choose to take part
in the movement can document and detail causing chaos and destruction of police
property in popular social media, but they must do so without inadvertently
exposing their true identity. Moreover, It is also important for people that are
unable physically to participate to be able to fund crippling the police anonymously and feel
certain that they are making a difference. I&#x27;ll list here certain tools and tricks that can help
maintain anonymity and provide plausible deniability.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;anonymous-communication-and-coordination-using-simplex-chat&quot;&gt;Anonymous communication and coordination using SimpleX chat&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SimpleX chat is &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;simplex.chat&#x2F;downloads&#x2F;&quot;&gt;cross platform&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; and requires
no identifiable information to use. It is end-to-end encrypted and retains
forward-secrecy. Here is a preliminary group chat link you can use to
communicate with like-minded people, although over time I advise people to form their own
tight-knit secret group chats to keep out undercover agents of the state. I
would also advise using &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;simplex.chat&#x2F;docs&#x2F;guide&#x2F;privacy-security.html#using-tor&quot;&gt;Tor (using the Orbot app) for further anonymity&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;img&#x2F;IMG_20240604_205447.png&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;anonymous-sending-of-funds-using-monero&quot;&gt;Anonymous sending of funds using Monero&lt;&#x2F;h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;web.getmonero.org&#x2F;&quot;&gt;Monero is an private cryptocurrency&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; with an
obfuscated blockchain. This means that for every transaction in the blockchain, unless you own the
right keys, the transaction sender, recepient and amount are obfuscated. This is
perfect for this usecase. Bitcoin is too dangerous to use for because of this
scenario:&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alice the Anarchist destroyed a police vehicle successfully, and in her video
documenting the process she announces her Bitcoin address to ask for
donations (let&#x27;s call her address &lt;strong&gt;1MWux&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;)&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The video becomes viral in Twitter and millions of Americans who support
Cripple the Police movement donate small amounts of Bitcoin to &lt;strong&gt;1MWux&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alice now wants to continue her rampage, but she ran out of funds. She&#x27;s now
planning to liquidate all her bitcoin from &lt;strong&gt;1MWux&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. She transfers her
Bitcoin from her wallet to a centralized exchange (Coinbase, Kraken, etc)
wallet (let&#x27;s call the centralized exchange wallet &lt;strong&gt;12wYYK&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;) and
obtains USD from there&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next day, her funds get frozen and the police swarm her house. The problem
with Bitcoin&#x27;s transparent blockchain the authorities are able to link the send address &lt;strong&gt;1MWux&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;
with the send address in the viral video, and due to crypto KYC laws the exchange
will be able to tie Alice&#x27;s real identity to &lt;strong&gt;1MWux&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using Monero, this transaction is obfuscated from the blockchain, meaning that
no trace of information about &lt;strong&gt;1MWux&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; will ever be in the blockchain due to stealth
addresses.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Monero also allows the creation of subaddress to receive funds that you can advertise so an
observer cannot link them. &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;anhdres.medium.com&#x2F;how-moneros-accounts-and-subaddresses-work-in-monerujo-4fa7df0a58e4&quot;&gt;Read more
here&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;
(Monerujo is a specific wallet app created for Android). &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrency is a tool for financial freedom (think, not geting funds frozen
using PayPal) and is an integral part of funding Cripple the Police. Monero is
the perfect tool for this case, but a perfect tool is not enough. Learning to
use the tool and improving your operational security (OpSec) is also necessary.
Finally, to liquidate Monero into usable funds, it is recommended to use a
decentralized exchange like &lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;github.com&#x2F;retoaccess1&#x2F;haveno-reto&#x2F;releases&#x2F;tag&#x2F;v1.0.6&quot;&gt;Haveno Reto&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For people interested in Cripple the Police, here&#x27;s an address you can donate to
to bootstrap the movement. The funds here will exclusively be used to award
bounties to people who have succesfully crippled the police, documented their
experience, and listed a Monero address (please do &lt;strong&gt;NOT&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt; reuse monero
addresses in this scenario. Create a new one for each instance of crippling the
police.) &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;img&#x2F;cripple.png&quot;&#x2F;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from this, we pledge to support pro-Palestinian protestors with gas masks
and protection from police crowd-control. Anything we can do to even the
playingfield and nullify the effect of police crowd control. Please contact us using the SimpleX
chat to see what we can do for you.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
